Viewers all over the world, begin to welcome him.
Holy Ghost, you are welcome.
Free our heart to welcome You.
Release our heart to welcome You.
Holy Ghost!
Release my heart to welcome You.
You are welcome - Holy Ghost!
You are welcome!
Holy Ghost!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Viewers, fear not; Jesus has defeated satan.
He has defeated sickness; He has defeated infirmity.
He has defeated poverty.
Yes! Fear not!
In the name of Jesus!
Right now, open your lips and begin to confess your victory.
Confess your victory over sickness; confess your victory over disease.
Confess your victory over infirmity; confess your victory over poverty.
Confess your victory over hardship; confess your victory over circumstances.
Begin to dominate circumstances around you.
Crisis, situation - dominate them!
Jesus has defeated satan.
Right now, open your lips - in the name of Jesus, be free!
I command your freedom, in the name of Jesus!
That sickness, that disease, wherever it is - be free, in the name of Jesus!
Every sickness, every spirit that attacks your body, that attacks your organs -
be free, in the name of Jesus!
I command them out!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Cheer up; Jesus has overcome!
Jesus has overcome!
Jesus has overcome for you!
Jesus has defeated satan for you!
I say, cheer up!
Every spirit that attacks your body, that attacks your spirit, that attacks your organs,
in your blood, in your kidneys, in your liver, in your fluids -
I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
I say, out!
You sickness - out!
You disease - out!
You infirmity - out!
I can see them out.
They are giving way.
Rejoice!
I can see them out.
I can see you being healed.
I can see you being delivered.
I can see you being saved.
I can't hear you.
[Amen!]
Let me hear your voice!
In the name of Jesus!
Speak to me - the voice of victory. I want to hear the voice of victory from you.
Voice of victory!
I'm free - defeat and failure are things of the past!
Let me hear your voice!
In the name of Jesus!
Rejoice!
Jesus has overcome!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
TT: Unknown
RV: Mel Flowers 25/08/2018